question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "David Baszucki was a co-founder of ROBLOX Corporation.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "In &quot;Call Of Duty: World At War&quot;, the first appearance of the &quot;PPSH-41&quot; in &quot;Zombies&quot; was in the map &quot;Der Riese&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "The game &quot;Jetpack Joyride&quot; was created by &quot;Redbrick Studios&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "Peter Molyneux was the founder of Bullfrog Productions.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "The Indie Game Development Studio Cing, developers of Hotel Dusk and Last Window, went bankrupt on March 1st, 2010.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon, Bulbasaur is the only starter pokemon that is a Grass\/Poison type.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "The Konami Code is known as Up, Up, Down, Down, Left, Right, Right, Left, B, A, Start.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "Unturned originally started as a Roblox game.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "The video game &quot;Fuel&quot; has an open world that is 5,560 square miles?", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "The shotgun appears in every numbered Resident Evil game.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "The first &quot;Metal Gear&quot; game was released for the PlayStation 1.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "&quot;Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater&quot; takes place on Shadow Moses Island.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "The main playable character of the 2015 RPG &quot;Undertale&quot; is a monster.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "Tetris is the #1 best-selling video game of all-time.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "Minecraft wasn&rsquo;t the original name to Minecraft.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "In Half-Life 2, if you play the zombies&#039; speech in reverse, they actually speak coherent English.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "In Until Dawn, both characters Sam and Mike cannot be killed under any means until the final chapter of the game.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "&quot;Half-Life 2&quot; runs on the Source Engine.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "In the game &quot;Subnautica&quot;, a &quot;Spadefish&quot; will attack you.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "In &quot;Super Mario Bros.&quot;, the clouds and bushes have the same artwork and are just different colors.", "correct_answer": "True",
                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "Resident Evil 4 was originally meant to be a Nintendo GameCube exclusive.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "In &quot;Mario Kart 64&quot;, Waluigi is a playable character.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "In the game &quot;Until Dawn&quot; Emily is the only playable character who can be killed by another playable character directly.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "In the game &quot;Melty Blood Actress Again Current Code&quot;, you can enter Blood Heat mode in Half Moon style.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "Donkey Kong was originally set to be a Popeye arcade game.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "The song &quot;Megalovania&quot; by Toby Fox made its third appearence in the 2015 RPG &quot;Undertale&quot;.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "Amazon acquired Twitch in August 2014 for $970 million dollars.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "In &quot;Resident Evil&quot;, only Chris has access to the grenade launcher.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "Nintendo&#039;s Luigi was originally just called Green Mario?", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "The ghosts in &quot;Pac-Man&quot; and &quot;Ms. Pac-Man&quot; have completely different behavior.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "The Mann Co. Store from Team Fortress 2 has the slogan &quot;We hire mercenaries and get in fights&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "In Splatoon, the Squid Sisters are named Tako and Yaki.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "The names of Tom Nook&#039;s cousins in the Animal Crossing franchise are named &quot;Timmy&quot; and &quot;Jimmy&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "Tony Hawk&#039;s Pro Skater was released in 1999.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "The main character in the &quot;Half-Life&quot; franchise is named Morgan Freeman.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "There are 2 player roles in Trouble in Terrorist Town.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "Watch_Dogs 2 is a prequel.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "Each piece in Tetris is called a tetris.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "In &quot;Overwatch,&quot; an allied McCree will say &quot;Step right up&quot; upon using his ultimate ability Deadeye.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "question": "&quot;Resident Evil 7&quot; is the first first-person Resident Evil game.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
